Well, he has such a trick, how he
Ну у него такая фишка есть как бы он
came up with such an original style in
придумал настолько оригинальный стиль в
this objective realism, it’s called, uh, a
этом объективном реализме называется
series of one-time
ээ сериал одноразовых
actors I’m from the city of Khmelnitsky You’re
актёров Я из города Хмельницкий Вы
from far away Well, more
откуда издалека Ну а
specifically, why? Well, I’m interested in
конкретнее А зачем Ну мне интересно с
what regions I communicated with people from, this is
каких регионов я с людьми общался я вот
how I imagine Russia simply
так представляю Россия просто
big
большая
Yes big Well where are you from what
Да большая Ну откуда вы с какого
region oh from Perm Well Perm region
региона ой с Пермского Ну Пермский край
Well it’s not so far Yeah I
Ну это не так далеко
understand you’re a Permian Mari Komi
Угу понял вы пермячка марийка Коми
what is your nationality
кто по нации
Yes I’m half Mari half
Да я наполовину марийка наполовину
Gypsy Gypsy I understand and you know the Mari or
цыганка цыганка понял а Марийский или
Gypsy language
цыганский язык
there a few words there I understand a couple of words  what are
там пару слов там пару слов понял о чём
you talking about here
общаетесь тут
girl? Well, I’m just looking for people with whom I
девица Ну просто ищу людей с которыми
can at least
можно хоть о том-то хоть О чём-то
talk about something normally. Let’s talk about something, besides
нормально пообщаться да давайте кроме
politics, besides all this oppression and the
политики кроме всего этого гнёта и тому
like. By the way, I don’t like talking about politics either
подобно Я кстати тоже о политике не
because everyone sees my flag like
люблю потому что все видят мой флаг типа
and  they immediately start quarreling about
и сразу о политике начинают ссориться а
politics, but I can only
политике я могу Разве что только
ask, for example, Do you think
спросить например вот Как вы считаете
whose
чей
Crimea is
Крым
anyone’s? Well, it was originally given to Ukraine,
ничей Ну изначально его подарили Украине
as it was
как это
originally given to
изначально даре его изначально подарили
Ukraine for nothing, and the gift is not taken away, then whose
Украине а дареное не забирается то чей
Crimea turns out to be Crimea belongs to Ukraine,
Крым получается Крым принадлежит Украине
but all of Russia thinks
но вся Россия считает
that
что
Russian s s
российский
everything is just politics and I don’t want to
с всё лишь политика и в это не хочу
delve into this you have any questions for me
вникать у вас какие-то вопросы ко мне
what do you generally like to do what do
есть чем вы вообще любите заниматься что
you like to read listen to psychology I
вы любите читать слушать психологией
do practical
занимаюсь практической
[music]
[музыка]
Yeah what kind of music do you like to listen to
Угу какую музыку любите слушать
classical
классическую
it develops It’s good You You  from
это развивает Это хорошо Вы Вы из
the classics that we
классики что
listened to
слушали
Bach, I also listened to Beethoven But
Баха Бетховена тоже слушала Но мне он
somehow he’s not for me, I’m more pshe yes I’m
как-то нет для меня я больше пше да Я
still more confused, Shan suits me better Yes,
вот ещё шапе пробол вот Шан мне больше
but no I’ve been
заходит Да вот но нет Я последнее время
putting off the classics for later why Well
отложила классику на потом почему Ну
now I like tin more  haven’t
сейчас больше мне нравится жесть а не
tried to play around with
пробовали побаловаться
the sheet No, I
листом Нет мне больше
like rock more, something informal
нравится рок что-то неформальное
lately I don’t know why Well, have
последнее время не знаю почему Ну а не
n’t you tried to listen there, for example,
не пробовали слушать там например
Mozart in rock
Моцарта в рок
arrangements Well, if the arrangement is different, it’s a
обработки Ну если обработка другая это
slightly different piece, it
уже немножко другое произведение
turns out it’s not a classic But there are
получается это не классика А есть вот
classics you should listen to from the very beginning  then
классику нужно слушать изначально то
what it should be like Yeah, in order to
какая она должна быть Угу чтобы её
understand it, to understand it Well, simple
понять что неё вникнуть понял Ну просто
And all these processing is something else
А все эти обработки - это уже другое
if you don’t understand and it doesn’t get into it for you
если ты не понимаешь и не вникает тебе
like NN, it doesn’t matter Yes, if it’s a different
НН типа там всё равно Да если другая
processing, then yes If you listen to the original,
обработка то да Если оригинал слушать то
you can delve into it  you can understand this, but
можно в это вникнуть можно это понять но
if it’s a different arrangement, it’s no longer
если это другая обработка уже не
original, it’s a slightly different
оригинальная это уже немножко другой
sound, a slightly different
звук немножко другая
interpretation of thoughts, your father
интерпретация мыслей у вас отец Кто по
was a
национальности был
gypsy by nationality. You just don’t look like a
циган Просто вы не похожи на
gypsy. Yes, because your mother,
цыганку Да потому что мать
Marik
Марик
Got it. There is another question you have for
Понял Есть ещё какой-то вопрос У вас ко
me.  yes, what kind of films do you like? In what
мне да какие вы фильмы любите В каком
genre do you like to watch films? And
жанре любите смотреть фильмы А есть у
I have one. I used to not really like
меня Я раньше не очень любил
cinema, but recently I’ve been watching the
кинематограф но С недавних пор смотрю
series by Robert Madra Jaga-Jaga
сериал Роберта мадра джага-джага
and he also has different ones, there are badabum
и ещё там у него разные есть бадабум
worms, in short, a specific genre in principle
черви короче специфический жанр в прин
no. But in principle  What specific genre do
нет А в принципе Какой конкретно жанр
you like best? Well, this
вам больше всего по душе Ну вот этот
genre is objective
жанр объективный
realism. Yeah, that is,
реализм
they showed what
Угу то есть там что показывали то что
can really happen, yes
реально может быть да да Вот именно Да у
yes.
Правде показы да да Вот Вы прям это
objective realism in
реально описывает объективный реализм у
our country means the founder Yes, the
нас значит основоположник Да
founder of this trend, he himself
основоположник этого направления он сам
was born in Ukraine now lives in Ukraine
родился в Украине сейчас живёт в Украине
yes There is this Robert Magyar Brody, he
да Вот есть такой Роберт мадяр броди он
first started making small videos
сначала начал делать небольшие ролики
like a short film and people At first they
так короткометражку и люди Сначала
thought Well, damn it’s like, who would
думали Ну блин типа ну кто будет такое
watch this objective realism of social
смотреть объективный реализм социальных
videos  It’s not all that realistic,
роликов не настолько всё реалистично да
and he has every
и у него каждый всё
story, he’s developed his own
сюжет он развил свою студию
cinematography studio now. Yes, they were allocated, he
кинематографии сейчас Да им выделили он
sort of collected donations to
как бы собирал донаты для того чтобы на
support domestic cinema, yes.
поддержку отечественного кинематографа
And now, well, to continue filming.
да А сейчас ну чтобы дальше снимать Дада
continue so that there would
финансы чтобы дальше продолжить де чтобы
be more cameramen Yes, so that it would be possible
операторов больше было Да чтобы можно
to make more videos yes Well, that’s
было больше роликов делать
understandable Well, he has such a trick,
да Ну это понятно Ну у него такая фишка
as if he came up with an original
есть как бы он придумал оригинальный
style in this objective realism, it’s
стиль в этом объективном реализме
called a series of one-time actors That
называется сериал одноразовых актёров То
is, his actors do not repeat from
есть у него актёры не повторяются из
episode to
серии к
episode, that’s if  watch the first films of the Germans,
серий это если первые фильмы й германики
you can say the same thing if
посмотреть можно сказать тоже самое если
only the first films watch further the
только первые фильмы посмотреть дальше
characters repeat further the actors
герои повторяют дальше актёры
repeat themselves but he really has it
повторяются но у него у него реально он
every day Now, yes, it’s been a
кажды каждый день Сейчас да вот уже там
year and a half where he
полтора года где он каждый день
releases an episode every day And not a single actor in
выпускает серию Да и ни одни актёры в
it  neither the stuntmen nor the actors are repeated,
нём не повторяются ни каскадёры ни
no one He has such a policy of
актёры никто Вот у него такая политика
one here he is, etc. You have to play
один вот ла него пр Ты должен отыграть
one episode and that’s it, but
одну серию и
this, well, on my part, this
всё но это ну с моей стороны это
deserves respect because a person
заслуживает уважения потому что человек
finds other people, finds other scripts,
находит людей других находит сценарии
does it all in his head,
это делает всё это в своей голове
writes it down  then after that he tries to
прописывает потом после этого пытается
film it, it’s too much work, it’s a difficult
снять это слишком большая работа сложная
job, it’s a very stressful job Yes,
работа это очень стрессовая работа Да
because yes, it deserves
потому что как бы да это заслуживает
a lot of respect in this regard,
очень огромного уважение в этом плане
because the person got confused, the person
потому что человек заморочился человек
did it so that the person just
сделал так чтобы человек просто
looked for some 5-10 minutes. No on this
посмотрел каких-то 5-10 минут Нон на это
killed one week Sorry
убил одну неделю Извините
for first of all Look at yes first of all yes
за во-первых Смотри во да во-первых да
In order to shoot this video you need
Для того чтобы снять этот ролик надо а
time - This is the most expensive thing
время - Это самое самое дорогое что у
we have we need We need to learn the cameramen
нас есть надо Надо выучить операторов
who will film Yes we need
которые будут снимать Да надо
technicians from what
техников какого
angle this is also explained to the actors how
ракурса это актёрам тоже объяснить как
them to play What emotions should there be
им играть Какие эмоции должны быть
besides this, there are also understudies, there are also
помимо этого есть ещё и дублёры есть ещё
editors who must edit
и монтажёры которые должны монтировать
so that it is all one whole, this is
так чтобы это всё было одним целым это
deep work, this is hard work and the
глубокая работа это тяжёлая работа и
people who do it all Yes, these are
люди которые этим всем занимаются Да это
worthy people, respect who are in
достойные люди уважение которые вот по
fact the ones we are watching  5-10 minutes of
факту которые мы смотрим 5-10 минут
people on This kills for a week, not just one
человек на Это убивает неделю не одну
person, not even just one person, a whole group of
даже не только человек целая группа
people For us to watch. For
людей Для того чтобы мы посмотрели Вот
example, 5 minutes of this episode of the series
например 5 минут этого серию сериала
po Yes, people kill more than one person,
ро Да люди убивают не один человек
they kill for this more than one week, and not a
убивают на это не одну неделю и ни
single person
одного человека
especially  whose idea because a
у особенно то чья идея потому что
person approaches this, a person spends
человек к этому подходит человек тратит
not only his resources, not only his
не только свои ресурсы не только Свои
emotional feelings, not only his
эмоциональные чувства не только
physical feelings, but also here
физические чувства но и ещё ещё ещё тут
the problem has become that now, yes now he, let’s
проблема стала что сейчас да сейчас он
say, began to very much
скажем начал очень сильно
popularize this genre Yes, uh,
популяризировать этот жанр Да ээ вот
disposable actors and so on  Now
одноразовых актёров так и сейчас очень
we have a lot of directors in Ukraine, too,
много у нас в Украине тоже режиссёров
there are beginners, there are more
там есть начинающие есть более там
advanced ones, there are entire film studios. They
продвинутые есть целые киностудия Они
actually shoot this content, they also
реально снимают этот контент тоже
create competition, and even in
конкуренцию делают да и у нас даже на
some areas, let’s say, we have a problem
некоторых скажем участках есть проблема
finding actors. So they can
найти актёров Вот они могут целый день э
try to find an actor all day long.  series Yes, there is nothing
пробовать найти актёра для серии Да
because there are already other
ничего нету потому что уже другие
directors Yes, we worked with these actors,
режиссёры Да отработали с этими актёрами
you understand this is normal because the actor
понимаете это нормально потому что актёр
cannot show the emotions that should
не не может выдать эмоции которые должны
be there, this is normal No, well, there
быть это нормально Не ну там с эмоциями
are no problems with the emotions of the actors, yes there are so many Well,
актёров нету проблем да там настолько Ну
they select very creative actors,
актёров они очень творческих подбирают
AK is boring, let’s say
АК приелось скажем
so these are films from the other side,
так это Это ж фильмы одно другой стороны
even if it is a one-off film where the
даже если это одноразовый фильм где
actor has already starred, if this film has already appeared,
актёр уже снялся если этот фильм зашёл
his face is already more recognizable and that’s why
его лицо уже более узнаваемо и поэтому
there there. The thing is that Look here in
там там Дело в том что Смотрите тут в
objective realism Yes, very often
объективном реализме Да очень часто
after filming the actor’s face is no longer recognizable.
после съёмки лицо актра уже не узнаваемо
there recently with
вот там недавно с
Damn so who is there skin we sweat Tsei video
Блин так кто там скине потим Цей ролик
Madyari yay VN
мадяри яй ВН
poshi more politely dumbfounded write on Tsei
поши важливе оголошення пишиться на Цей
reserve channel Andriy Popik chatroulette
резервний канал Андрий Попик чатрулетка
I created another channel on yak treasure
я створив ще один канал на який клада
unique video I didn’t bother either on Tsyomu
уникальни вдео я не були ни на цьому
Kan or on streams write Nago there
кана ни на стримах пишиться Наго там
every day  will come out Novy and but video
кожен день будуть выходи Нови и но видео
squeak comment skinny video so YouTube yogo
писка комент кожным вдео щоб YouTube
effektivni
його ефективни
pass that channel so that more
просувати той канал для того щоб бильше
people can take information from our videos
людей отримувало информацию з наших вдео
so that Tsey our channel Yes YouTube bits
тому що Цей наш канал Да трошки YouTube
having driven your ban mi we will try more
загнав твий бан ми будем пробу ще
in parallel to work one
паралельно робити один
write
пиши